KOLOTKO VLADYSLAV

Mobile: +48 453 333 446; +38 098 856 25 45; +38 066 881 95 58 (Viber, Telegram)

E-mail: smvk.fox@gmail.com

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/vladyslav-k-071a491b5/

CV: https://vladka-k.github.io/en.html

DATE OF BIRTH: August 16, 1990, Kharkiv, Ukraine

ABOUT ME:

Since March 2021, I have been working as a Front End/Markup (HTML, CSS) developer on projects for the European and American markets, focusing on creating responsive, and visually appealing web interfaces. My work includes developing sections and pages of websites based on Figma layouts, utilizing technologies such as HTML, SCSS, Tailwind, jQuery, and JavaScript to ensure precision and seamless functionality. I am involved in web projects by developing and refining existing blocks, sections, components, and pages. In addition, I am involved in styling standard WordPress components according to design specifications, maintaining uniformity across the websites.

In 2020, completed two courses at Source IT: Markup Development (HTML + CSS) and Front End Development.

Since 2018 I worked as SEO specialist in the internet marketing agency. I started as SEO assistant with minimal knowledge and no experience in this field.

In 2013 graduated from KhNEU with a degree in Administrative Management ("Master" level).

WORK EXPERIENCE:

May 2021 - Present

WWWEst Solutions Markup/Front End Developer

Main responsibilities:

- development of sections and pages of websites according to Figma layouts (HTML, CSS/SCSS, Tailwind, Bootstrap, jQuery, JavaScript);
- optimization of accessibility of blocks and elements for users and screen readers;
- development of existing blocks, sections, components and pages of websites;
- styling standard WordPress components according to layouts;
- fixing bugs and inconsistencies between website pages and layout.

Activity results:

Deepened the practical skills of website page layout on real projects, deepened the skills of working with Git, got practical skills in teamwork on projects.

March 2021 - April 2021

Dream Dev Solutions Junior Front End Developer

Main responsibilities:

- creating pages by layout (HTML, SCSS, jQuery plugins);
- creation network of information web sites on CMS Word Press (Elementor, Gutenberg);

• adding new pages to existing web sites on the CMS Word Press (Elementor).

Activity results:

Got practical skills in page markup on real projects, page markup using BEM principles, mobile first, pixel perfect, skills in working with Git, basic skills in working with the Gulp project collector.

May 2018 – February 2021

Full Cycle Internet Marketing Agency «Big Fish Agency» SEO specialist

Main responsibilities:

- technical edits and improvements to the appearance and functionality of sites (edits via CMS and code);
- work aimed at site optimization (site audit, collection of the semantic core, distribution of the semantic core among pages, the introduction of meta tags, the introduction of linking, the purchase of links from donor sites, etc.);
- tracking and analysis of positions for key queries.

Activity results:

Deepened knowledge and skills of working with HyperText Markup Language (HTML) and Cascading Style Sheets (CSS). Got skills in CMS Word Press, Open Cart, Joomla, MODX.

November 2016 – July 2018

Wholesale online store Parfum Land Co-Founder / Site Administrator / SEO Specialist

Main responsibilities:

- management and completion of the online store on the CMS Joomla;
- creating and maintaining accounts and groups in social networks;
- work with Google products (Google Analytics, Google Search Console, Google My Business, Google AdWords).

Activity results:

Got skills in working with an online store, in CMS Joomla, basic knowledge and skills in working with standardized HTML markup language and cascading CSS style sheets, skills in site optimization for search engines.

EDUCATION:

September 2007 – January 2013

KHARKOV NATIONAL ECONOMIC UNIVERSITY (KhNEU), KHARKOV

Faculty: «Management and Marketing». Specialty: Administrative management.

Received the educational qualification level «Master»

COURSES:

Markup (HTML+CSS), Front End – Source IT

SKILLS:

- skills in working with HTML5 and CSS3;
- skills of working with Prepros SCSS;

- skills in working with the Git version control system;
- skills in working with the Bootstrap, Tailwind frameworks;
- knowledge and skills of working with JS, jQuery;
- skills in Figma, Avocode, Photoshop;
- skills of working with CMS Word Press;
- English Intermediate (B1).